A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of the Medical Letter publication, 1986-1995 FA1103
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University collection of the Medical Letter publication
1986-1995
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University.
Medical Letter, Inc
FA1103
135.6 Cubic Feet 113 standard record storage boxes
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 25 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are open at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 891-U
Other Finding Aids
For additional Medical Letter materials open for research see:
FA241 Rockefeller University collection of the Medical Lettter publication
Scope and Contents
Contents includes: original manuscripts, reprints, advertising and package inserts, sources check, consultatnts drafts, manufacturers replies, and bibliography.
Biographical / Historical
The Medical Letter on Drugs and Therapeutics is an independent, non-profit publication providing unbiased critical evaluation of drugs in terms of their effectiveness, adverse effects and possible alternative medications.
- TML, 28-1 - Generic Drugs, 1986 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 28-2 - Antimicrobial susceptibility tests, 1986 January 3 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 28-5 - Tests for occult blood, 1986 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 28-6 - Drugs for Tuberculosis, 1986 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 28-8 - Potency-sparing radical prostatectomy, 1986 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 28-9 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1986 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- TML, 28-9 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1986 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 28-19 - Flecainide - a new antiarrhythmic drug, 1986 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 28-20 - Choice of a beta-blocker, 1986 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 28-22 - Prevention of bacterial endocarditis, 1986 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- TML, 28-23 - Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases, 1986 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 28-23 - Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases, 1986 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 28-29 - Imipenem-cilastin sodium (Primaxin), 1986 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 28-31 - Asprin to prevent myocardial infarction and death, 1986 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 28-32 - Nitrofurantoin in pregnancy, 1986 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- TML, 28-33 - The Choice of antimicrobial drugs, 1986 March 28 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 28-41 - Drugs for treatment of systemic fungal infections, 1986 April 11 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 28-41 - Drugs for treatment of systemic fungal infections, 1986 April 11 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 28-45 - Two new beta-blockers for glaucoma, 1986 April 25 (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 28-46 - Ribavirin (Virazole), 1986 April 25 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 28-48 - Potassium citrate tablets for nephrolithiasis, 1986 April 25 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 28-49 - Amiodarane, 1986 May 9 (Box 4, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 28-51 - Drugs that cause photosensitivity, 1986 May 9 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 28-51 - Drugs that cause photosensitivity, 1986 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- TML, 28-53 - Enalapril for hypertension, 1986 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 28-55 - Suprofen, 1986 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 28-56 - Buprenorphine, 1986 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 9-12)
- TML 28-57 - Clobetasol - a potent new topical corticosteroid, 1986 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 28-59 - Oral nytroglycerin spray, 1986 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 28-61 - Ketoprofen, 1986 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 28-62 - Drugs for Parkinsonism, 1986 June 20 (Box 6, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 28-65 - Mexiletine for arrhythiasm, 1986 July 4 (Box 6, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 28-68 - Butoconazole for vulvovaginal candidiasis, 1986 July 4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- TML, 28-67 - Trientine for Wilson's disease, 1986 July 4 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 28-69 - Crack Cocaine, 1986 July 18 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 28-70 - Cefotetan disodium (Cefotan), 1986 July 18 (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 28-73 - Midazolam, 1986 August 1 (Box 7, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 28-74 - Sulfites in drugs and food, 1986 August 1 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 28-75 - Treatment of alcohol withdrawal, 1986 August 1 (Box 7, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 28-77 - A Gastric balloon for treatment of obesity, 1986 August 15 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 28-78 - Interferon for treatment of hairy-cell leukemia, 1986 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 28-80 - Hemoperfusion for removal of toxins, 1986 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 28-81 - Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms, 1986 August 29 (Box 8, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 28-87 - Digoxin antibody fragments for digitalis toxicity, 1986 September 12 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
- TML 28-88 - Carnitine, 1986 September 12 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- TML 28-88 - Carnitine, 1986 September 12 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 28-89 - Permethrin for head lice, 1986 September 12 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 28-91 - Drugs for epilepsy, 1986 September 26 (Box 9, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 28-95 - Prevention of influenza, 1986-1987, 1986 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 28-97 - Monoclonal antibodies for kidney allograft rejection, 1986 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 28-99 - Drugs for psychiatric disorders, 1986 October 24 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
- TML, 28-107 - Azidothymidine for AIDS, 1986 November 7 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- TML, 28-109 - Electrical current for excessive sweating, 1986 November 7 (Box 10, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 28-111 - Drugs for cardiac arrythmias, 1986 November 21 (Box 10, Folder 11-17)
- TML, 28-117 - Buspirone - a non-benzodiazepine for anxiety, 1986 December 5 (Box 11, Folder 1-9)
- TML, 28-118 - Recombinant hepatitis B vaccine, 1986 December 5 (Box 11, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 28-119 - Transdermal estrogen, 1986 December 5 (Box 11, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 28-121 - New preparations of vancomycin, 1986 December 19 (Box 11, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 28-123 - Treatment of hypothermia, 1986 December 19 (Box 11, Folder 19-21)
- Handbook of antimicrobial therapy (Revised), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1-6)
- TML, 23-40 - Desensitization of poison ivy, 1981 April 17 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 26-44 - Antimicrobial susceptibility tests, 1984 April 27 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- TML, 26-59 - Nitroglycerin patches, 1984 June 22 (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 28-110 - Quinin for night cramps, 1986 November 7 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- TML, 29-1 - Drugs for hypertension, 1987 January 2 (Box 12, Folder 13-18)
- TML, 29-7 - Fish Oils for the heart, 1987 January 16 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 29-9 - Etretinate for psoriasis, 1987 January 16 (Box 13, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 29-11 - Drugs for asthma, 1987 January 30 (Box 13, Folder 8-15)
- TML, 29-17 - Famotidine (Pepcid), 1987 February 13 (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 29-17 - Famotidine (Pepcid), 1987 February 13 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 29-18 - Drugs for hypertensive emergencies, 1987 February 13 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- TML, 29-21 - Druges for rheumatoid arthritis, 1987 February 27 (Box 14, Folder 5-11)
- TML, 29-25 - Norfloxacin (Noroxin), 1987 March 13 (Box 14, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 29-27 - Drugs for migraine, 1987 March 13 (Box 14, Folder 16-19)
- TML, 29-29 - Cancer chemotherapy, 1987 March 27 (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
- TML, 29-37 - Verapamil for hypertension, 1987 April 10 (Box 15, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 29-39 - Transmucosal controlled-release nitroglycerine, 1987 April 10 (Box 15, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 29-41 - Serum cholesterol determinators, 1987 April 24 (Box 15, Folder 16-19)
- TML, 29-42 - Alclometasone, 1987 April 24 (Box 15, Folder 20-21)
- TML, 29-43 - New contrast media, 1987 April 24 (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 29-45 - Aztreonam (Azactam), 1987 May 8 (Box 16, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 29-47 - Human calcitonin for Paget's disease, 1987 May 8 (Box 16, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 29-49 - Guanfacine for hypertension, 1987 May 22 (Box 16, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 29-50 - Encainide for cardiac arrhyhtmias, 1987 May 22 (Box 16, Folder 16-19)
- TML, 29-52 - Monooctanoin for gallstones, 1987 May 22 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- TML, 29-52 - Monooctanoin for gallstones, 1987 May 22 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- TML, 29-53 - Advice for travelers, 1987 June 5 (Box 17, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 29-57 - Esmolol - a short-acting IV beta-blocker, 1987 June 19 (Box 17, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 29-58 - Flurbiprofen - an ophthalmic NSAID, 1987 June 19 (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 29-59 - Alfentanil, 1987 June 19 (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 29-60 - Methacholine for diagnosis of asthma, 1987 June 19 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 29-61 - Safety of antimicrobial drugs in pregnancy, 1987 July 3 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 29-63 - Oral fluids for dehydration, 1987 July 3 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 29-65 - Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction, 1987 July 17 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- TML, 29-65 - Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction, 1987 July 17 (Box 18, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 29-71 - Ipratropium, 1987 July 31 (Box 18, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 29-73 - A new biosynthetic human growth hormone, 1987 July 31 (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 29-75 - Prevention and treatment of postmenopausal osteoporosis, 1987 August 14 (Box 18, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 29-77 - Clofazimine for leprosy and mycobacterium avium complex infections, 1987 August 14 (Box 18, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 29-78 - Advice for travelers - Immune globulin for prevention of hepatitis A, 1987 August 14 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- TML, 29-79 - Ampicillin (sulbactam) (Unasyn), 1987 August 28 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- TML, 29-79 - Ampicillin (sulbactam) (Unasyn), 1987 August 28 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 29-81 - Influenza prevention, 1987-1988, 1987 August 28 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 29-83 - Treatment of acute drug abuse reactions, 1987 September 11 (Box 19, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 29-87 - Topical minoxidil for baldness, 1987 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 29-88 - Interleukin-2, 1987 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 29-89 - Tranexamic acid, 1987 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 29-91 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1987 October 9 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 29-91 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1987 October 9 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 29-95 - Intracavernous injections for impotence, 1987 October 23 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 29-96 - Mometasone - a new topical steroid, 1987 October 23 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
- TML, 29-99 - Lovastatin for hypercholeterolemia, 1987 November 6 (Box 20, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 29-101 - Botulinum toxin injection for ocular muscle disorders, 1987 November 6 (Box 20, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 29-103 - Treatment of pneumocystis carinii pneumonia, 1987 November 20 (Box 20, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 29-105 - Choice of antihistamines for allergic rhinitis, 1987 November 20 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 29-107 - Tissue-type plasminogen activator for acute coronary thrombosis, 1987 December 4 (Box 21, Folder 4-8)
- TML, 29-109 - Prevention of bacterial endocarditis, 1987 December 4 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- TML, 29-111 - Suction-assisted lipectomy, 1987 December 18 (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 29-112 - Hypertension, 1987 December 18 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter, revised edition, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 29-113 - Update on AZT, 1987 December 18 (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 29-113 - Update on AZT, 1987 December 18 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-1 - Monoclate - a purified antihemophhilic factor, 1988 January 1 (Box 22, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 30-5 - Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases, 1988 January 15 (Box 22, Folder 6-11)
- TML, 30-11 - Ciprofloxacin, 1988 January 29 (Box 22, Folder 12-16)
- TML, 30-13 - Vasodilators for chronic congestive heart failure, 1988 January 29 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- TML, 30-13 - Vasodilators for chronic congestive heart failure, 1988 January 29 (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 30-15 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1988 February 12 (Box 23, Folder 4-14)
- TML, 30-25 - New copper IUD, 1988 February 26 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 30-25 - New copper IUD, 1988 February 26 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-26 - Choice of benzodiazepines, 1988 February 26 (Box 24, Folder 3-10)
- TML - 30-29 - Alpha 1-proteinase inhibitor for alpha 1-antitrypsin deficiency, 1988 March 11 (Box 24, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 30-30 - Drugs for treatment of deep fungal infections, 1988 March 11 (Box 24, Folder 14-17)
- TML, 30-33 - The Choice of antimicrobial drugs, 1988 March 25 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- TML, 30-33 - The Choice of antimicrobial drugs, 1988 March 25 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 30-41 - Lisinopril for hypertension, 1988 April 8 (Box 25, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 30-43 - Drugs for tuberculosis, 1988 April 8 (Box 25, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 30-45 - Fluxetine for depression, 1988 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 30-47 - Conjugated haemophilis influenzae type b vaccine, 1988 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 16-19)
- TML, 30-49 - Generic topical corticosteroids, 1988 May 6 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-50 - A more potent inactivated polio vaccine, 1988 May 6 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 30-51 - Methylphenidate revisited, 1988 May 6 (Box 26, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 30-53 - Masalamine for ulcerative colitis, 1988 May 20 (Box 26, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 30-55 - Mupirocin - a new topical antibiotic, 1988 May 20 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 30-57 - Cefuroxime axetil, 1988 June 3 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 30-57 - Cefuroxime axetil, 1988 June 3 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-59 - Perinatal toxicity of cacine, 1988 June 3 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 30-60 - Hemo M - a new antihemophilic factor, 1988 June 3 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- TML, 30-61 - Sunscreens, 1988 June 17 (Box 27, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 30-63 - Microx, 1988 June 19 (Box 27, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 30-65 - Treatment of Lyme disease, 1988 July 1 (Box 27, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 30-67 - Mitoxatone, 1988 July 1 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 30-67 - Mitoxatone, 1988 July 1 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-69 - Tretinoin for aging skin, 1988 July 15 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 30-70 - Interferon for treatment of genital warts, 1988 July 15 (Box 28, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 30-73 - Diagnostic tests for AIDS, 1988 July 29 (Box 28, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 30-74 - Treatment of xerostomia, 1988 July 29 (Box 28, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 30-77 - Nizatidine (Axid). TML, 30-92 - Ranitidine - a clarification, 1988 August 12 and September 23 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 30-79 - Penicillin allergy, 1988 August 12 (Box 29, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 30-81 - Ursodiol for dissolving gallstones, 1988 August 26 (Box 29, Folder 7-11)
- TML, 30-83 - Influenza prevention, 1988 August 26 (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 30-81 - Choice of cholesterol-lowering drugs, 1988 September 9 (Box 29, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 30-81 - Choice of cholesterol-lowering drugs, 1988 September 9 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-89 - High altitude sickness, 1988 September 23 (Box 30, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 30-91 - Metrodine and other drugs that induce ovulation, 1988 September 23 (Box 30, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 30-93 - The cervical cap. TML, 30-116 - The cervical cap - an additional note, 1988 October 7 and December 16 (Box 30, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 30-96 - Extracorporeal photochemotherapy for cutaneous T-cell lymphoma, 1988 October 7 (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 30-97 - ACE inhibitors for congestive heart-failure, 1988 October 21 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- TML, 30-97 - ACE inhibitors for congestive heart-failure, 1988 October 21 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 30-98 - Naftifine for fungal skin infections, 1988 October 21 (Box 31, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 30-100 - Cytomegalovirus immune globulin, 1988 October 21 (Box 31, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 30-101 - Meters for glucose monitoring, 1988 November 4 (Box 31, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 30-102 - Clomipramine for obsessive compulsive disorder, 1988 November 4 (Box 31, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 30-105 - Choice of contraceptives, 1988 November 18 (Box 31, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 30-105 - Choice of contraceptives. TML, 30-120 - Contraceptive correction, 1988 November 18 and December 30 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 30-109 - Diclofenac, 1988 December 2 (Box 32, Folder 4-7)
- TML, Special Publications - Handbook of Antimicrobial Therarpy (Revised Edition), 1988 (Box 32, Folder 8-14)
- TML, 30-2 - Antiemetics - Nabilone and other antiemetics for cancer patients, 1988 January 1 (Box 32, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 30-2 - Antiemetics - Nabilone and other antiemetics for cancer patients, 1988 January 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- TML, 30-117 - Insulin, Administration, Novolinpen for insulin injection, 1988 December 30 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- TML, 30-113 - Parkinson's Disease, Chemotherapy, Drugs for parkinsonism, 1988 December 30 (Box 33, Folder 3-7)
- TML, 30-116 - Sweetners, Artificial - Acesulfame - A new Artificial Sweetner, 1989 December 16 (Box 33, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 30-118 - Terconazole for candida vaginitis, 1988 December 30 (Box 33, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 30-119 - Diagnostics Tests, Ektachem analyzers for the office, 1988 December 30 (Box 33, Folder 14-16)
- TML 19-77 - Saccharin and chemical carcinogenesis, 1977 September 9 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- TML 19-77 - Saccharin and chemical carcinogenesis, 1977 September 9 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 31-1 - Epilepsy - Drugs for epilepsy, 1989 January 13 (Box 34, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 31-5 - Trimetrexate for pneumocystis carinii pneumonia, 1989 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 31-6 - Dexamethasone for bacterial meningitis in children, 1989 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 31-7 - Tiopronin for cystinuria, 1989 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- TML, 31-8 - The Viralizer for the common cold, 1989 January 27 (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 31-9 - Lithotripsy, Extracorporeal shock-wave lithotripsy for gallbladder stones, 1989 February 10 (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 31-11 - Drug Interactions, Foods interacting with MAO inhibitors, 1989 February 10 (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 31-13 - Psychopharmacological agents, Drugs for psychiatric disorders, 1989 February 24 (Box 35, Folder 6-13)
- TML, 31-21 - Misoprostol, 1989 March 10 (Box 35, Folder 14-17)
- TML, 31-22 - Obesity - Formula diets for obesity, 1989 March 10 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 31-23 - Hypnotics - Oral hypnotic drugs, 1989 March 10 (Box 36, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 31-25 - Hypertension - Drugs for hypertension, 1989 March 24 (Box 36, Folder 8-13)
- TML, 31-31 - Flurbiprofen, 1989 April 7 (Box 36, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 31-32 - Hypertension - Drugs for hypertensive emergencies, 1989 April 7 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- TML, 31-32 - Hypertension - Drugs for hypertensive emergencies, 1989 April 7 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 31-35 - Arrhythmias - Drugs for cardiac arrhythmias; and TML, 31-48 - Drugs for cardiac arrythmias - new warning, 1989 April 21 and May 19 (Box 37, Folder 3-8)
- TML, 31-41 - Nicardipine - a new calcium-entry blocker, 1989 May 5 (Box 37, Folder 9-13)
- TML, 31-43 - Antihistamines - Astemizole - another non-sedating antihistamine, 1989 May 5 (Box 37, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 31-45 - Insect repellents; and TML, 31-68 - Cancer - Cancer Chemotherapy - Correction, 1989 May 19 and July 14 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- TML, 31-45 - Insect repellents; and TML, 31-68 - Cancer - Cancer Chemotherapy - Correction, 1989 May 19 and July 14 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 31-47 - Nimodipine for cerebral vasospasm after subarachnoid hemmorrhage, 1989 May 19 (Box 38, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 31-49 - Cancer - Cancer Chemotherapy; and TML, 31-68 - Cancer - Cancer Chemotherapy - Correction, 1989 June 2 (Box 38, Folder 7-11)
- TML, 31-57 - Lyme disease - Treatment of lyme disease, 1989 June 16 (Box 38, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 31-59 - Sunscreens - Photoplex - a broad spectrum sunscreen, 1989 June 16 (Box 38, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 31-59 - Sunscreens - Photoplex - a broad spectrum sunscreen, 1989 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- TML, 31-61 - Arthritis - Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 1989 June 30 (Box 39, Folder 2-6)
- TML, 31-65 - Nitroglycerine - Nitroglycerine patches - do they work, 1989 July 14 (Box 39, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 31-66 - Octreotide - a synthetic somatostatin, 1989 July 14 (Box 39, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 31-69 - Measles - Measles revaccination; and TML, 31-88 - Measles - Measles revaccination - an additional note, 1989 July 28 and September 22 (Box 39, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 31-72 - Flutamide for prostate cancer, 1989 July 28 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- TML, 31-72 - Flutamide for prostate cancer, 1989 July 28 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- TML, 31-73 - Cephalosporins - Cefixime - a new oral cephalosporin, 1989 August 11 (Box 40, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 31-75 - Metronidazole - Topical metronidazole for rosacea, 1989 August 11 (Box 40, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 31-77 - Aspirin for prevention of myocardial infarction and stroke, 1989 August 25 (Box 40, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 31-79 - Ganciclovir, 1989 August 25 (Box 40, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 31-81 - Parkinson's Disease - Pergolide and selegiline for Parkinson's disease, 1989 September 8 (Box 40, Folder 16-19)
- TML, 31-81 - Parkinson's Disease - Pergolide and selegiline for Parkinson's disease, 1989 September 8 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 31-83 - Carboplatin, 1989 September 8 (Box 41, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 31-85 - Erythopoietin for anemia, 1989 September 22 (Box 41, Folder 7-11)
- TML, 31-87 - Contrast Media - Low osmolality contrast agents, 1989 September 22 (Box 41, Folder 2-16)
- TML, 31-89 - Levamisole with fluorouracil for colon cancer, 1989 October 6 (Box 41, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 31-91 - Pentamidine aerosol to prevent pneumocystis carinii pneumonia, 1989 October 6 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- TML, 31-91 - Pentamidine aerosol to prevent pneumocystis carinii pneumonia, 1989 October 6 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 30-94 - Pneumocystis Carinii - Prevention of pneumocystis carinii pneumonia, 1988 October 7 (Box 42, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 31-90 - Diagnostic tests - The Reflotron for office chemistries, 1989 October 6 (Box 42, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 31-93 - Contraceptives - Orval as a "morning after" contraceptive, 1989 October 20 (Box 42, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 31-94 - Clostridium Difficile Infections - Treatment of clostridium difficle diarrhea, 1989 October 20 (Box 42, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 31-95 - Influenza prevention, 1989 October 20 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 31-97 - Bupropion for depression, 1989 November 3 (Box 42, Folder 17-21)
- TML, 31-98 - Ifosfamide and mesna, 1989 November 3 (Box 42, Folder 22-24)
- TML, 31-98 - Ifosfamide and mesna, 1989 November 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- TML, 31-99 - Ethanolamine for esophageal varices, 1989 November 3 (Box 43, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 31-70 - Hypertension - Carteolol and penbutolol for hypertension, 1989 July 28 (Box 43, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 31-101 - Calcium supplements, 1989 November 17 (Box 43, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 31-103 - Is indapamide safer than a thiazide, 1989 November 17 (Box 43, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 31-104 - Analgesics - Patient controlled analgesia, 1989 November 17 (Box 43, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 31-105 - Antimicrobials - Antimicrobial prophlaxis in surgery, 1989 December 1 (Box 43, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 31-105 - Antimicrobials - Antimicrobial prophlaxis in surgery, 1989 December 1 (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 31-109 - Ibuprofen vs. acetaminophen in children, 1989 December 15 (Box 44, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 30-111 - Cholesterol lowering - Oat bran for lowering blood lipids, 1988 December 2 (Box 44, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 31-112 - Antimicrobials - Prevention of bacterial endocarditis, 1989 December 15 (Box 44, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 31-113 - Drugs, Injurious Effects - Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms, 1989 December 29 (Box 44, Folder 12-13)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition), 1989 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition) - Drugs for Asthma, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 15-17)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition) - Drugs for Asthma, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1-4)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice from the Medical Letter (Revised Edition) - Drugs for Migraine, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 5-8)